<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"><channel><title>The Gray Matter (James)</title><link>http://gray.net.au/</link><description></description><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2014 17:50:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>http://getnikola.com/</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>New Beginnings</title><link>http://gray.net.au/posts/new-beginnings.html</link><dc:creator>James Gray</dc:creator><description>&lt;p&gt;Most people who know me, know I have spent the last 3 years working hard in
various projects for my employer.  This has been a wonderful experience where
I learnt a lot, made heaps of new friends and achieved some great things.  I
spent time working in the USA, and got to explore some great landmarks on both
the east and west coasts!  It has been a good ride.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;However, as they say, all good things must come to an end and for me, the good
times dried up over a year ago.  I have persisted in trying to rekindle that
spark, but the reality became my work/life balance was more a "work=life"
equation.  I was spending progressively less time with my wonderful family,
and even less time with my friends or indulging in activities I value and
derive a lot of pleasure from, such as SCUBA diving.  So I made a tough
decision and resigned.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My original plan was to use the time between work commitments to fulfil a
long-term goal (so might say "dream") to become a SCUBA instructor.  The
course was booked, arrangements made, travel planned and paid for.  We were
going to Port Vila, Vanuatu!  Note all this is past tense.  Less than one week
from signing off at my last job I had an accident and badly broke my shoulder.
All plans cancelled.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So there is now this void between what I had planned, and the reality of the
current situation.  I can't even tie my own shoelaces or drive a car at the
moment, let alone engage in anything as onerous as diving.  Consequently I
have entered a bit of a holding pattern whilst I wait for my body to heal.
I'm not really sure what I'm supposed to do with all this free time, but
overhauling my personal website has been on my to-do list for a while.  Mind
you, typing with one hand for short periods has meant it has taken the better
part of 2 weeks to do what should've been possible in a few hours!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next chapter in my life has been hidden behind a veil of injury at the
moment and I eagerly look forward to seeing what, and more interestingly,
&lt;em&gt;how&lt;/em&gt; that chapter unfolds!&lt;/p&gt;</description><category>James</category><category>blog</category><guid>http://gray.net.au/posts/new-beginnings.html</guid><pubDate>Sat, 30 Aug 2014 04:01:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>